Pratik Patel



Cyber security

207 simcoe street north, Oshawa, Canada, L1G 4C6 / (647) 291 3073 / pratikpatel4388@gmail.com

Professional summary

Multipurpose IT specialist with a Bachelor's degree in computer applications and specialized training in software quality assurance. Right now, developing cybersecurity knowledge with an emphasis on network security and ethical hacking. Excited to apply this combined expertise to support dynamic IT initiatives efficiently.

Skills

Web Design

Design Thinking
Front End Coding

Software Assurance and Testing

Cyber Security Tools

Computer Literacy
Problem-Solving

Strong Communication

Employment history

SEP 2024 - PRESENT OSHAWA, CANADA

Team Member, Chaalo Oshawa

- Ensure workplace cleanliness for safety and efficiency, boosting team productivity.
- Adapt to various stations based on team demands, enhancing operational flexibility.
- Cultivate strong customer relationships through attentive service and friendly greetings.

JUL 2021 - JUL 2024 NAVSARI, INDIA

Full Stack Developer, Tech-Fusion Technologies

- Design user interactions and structures for web pages, enhancing user engagement.
- Develop APIs and reusable code, improving software efficiency and maintainability.
- Collaborate with graphic designers, ensuring cohesive and consistent brand design.
- Troubleshoot and upgrade software, resolving issues and optimizing performance.
- Create technical documentation, aiding in clear communication and project reporting.

Education

JUN 2017 - JUL 2021

NAVSARI, INDIA

SEP 2024 - PRESENT

OSHAWA, CANADA

Bachelor of Engineering(BE) in Computer Engineering, S S Agrawal College

Post Graduate Certificate in Cyber Security, DURHAM COLLEGE

Certificates

SEP 2021 - OCT 2022

Web Application Development at IIHT, Navsari